Governor's Efficiency Study Commission SR.397
State Archives of North Carolina
- Working Files, SR.397.3; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
  - Military and Veteran's Affairs, Department of, 11; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Administrative Introduction (folder 1 of 2), 1973; 3804; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Introduction (folder 1 of 2))
    - Administrative Introduction (folder 2 of 2), 1973; 3805; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Introduction (folder 2 of 2))
    - Civil Defense Agency, 1970-1972; 3806; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Civil Defense Agency)
    - Civil Defense Agency Recommendation Report, 1973; 3807; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Civil Defense Agency Recommendation Report)
    - Individual Recommendations and Progress Reports, 1973-1974; 3808; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Individual Recommendations and Progress Reports)
    - Kiefer File, 1970-1973; 3809; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Kiefer File)
    - Organization, 1974-1973; 3810; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Organization)
    - Position Descriptions, 1951-1973; 3811; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Position Descriptions)
    - Recommendations: Implemented, 1973; 3812; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Implemented)
    - Recommendations: In Process, 1973; 3813; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: In Process)
    - Recommendations: More Study, 1973; 3814; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: More Study)
    - Recommendations: Unacceptable, 1973; 3815; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Unacceptable)
  - Natural and Economic Resources, Department of, 12; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Administrative Services, 1971, 1973; 3816; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Services)
    - Administrative Services: Accounts Payable, 1973; 3817; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Services: Accounts Payable)
    - Administrative Services: Cost Accounting, 1973; 3818; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Services: Cost Accounting)
    - Administrative Services: Forestry Division, 1973; 3819; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Services: Forestry Division)
    - Administrative Services: Miscellaneous, 1973; 3820; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Services: Miscellaneous)
    - Administrative Services: Organizational Charts, 1972-1973; 3821; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Services: Organizational Charts)
    - Administrative Services: Personnel, 1971-1973; 3822; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Services: Personnel)
    - Administrative Services: Personnel Job Classifications, 1971-1973; 3823; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Services: Personnel Job Classifications)
    - Administrative Services: Physical Services, 1973; 3824; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Services: Physical Services)
    - Administrative Services: Public Affairs, 1973; 3825; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Services: Public Affairs)
    - Administrative Services: Recommendations, 1973; 3826; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Services: Recommendations)
    - Commerce and Industry, 1972-1975; 3827; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commerce and Industry)
    - Commercial and Sports Fisheries (folder 1 of 2), 1971-1973; 3828; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commercial and Sports Fisheries (folder 1 of 2))
    - Commercial and Sports Fisheries (folder 2 of 2), 1972-1973; 3829; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commercial and Sports Fisheries (folder 2 of 2))
    - Community Service, 1972-1973; 3830; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Community Service)
    - Implementation Progress Reports, 1973-1975; 3831; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Implementation Progress Reports)
    - Industry, Tourism and Community Resources, 1972-1973; 3832; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Industry, Tourism and Community Resources)
    - Industry, Tourism and Community Resources: Notes on Reorganization, 1973; 3833; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Industry, Tourism and Community Resources: Notes on Reorganization)
    - Job Classifications, 1973; 3834; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Job Classifications)
    - Office of Recreation Resources (folder 1 of 2), 1972-1973; 3835; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Office of Recreation Resources (folder 1 of 2))
    - Office of Recreation Resources (folder 2 of 2), 1963-1973; 3836; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Office of Recreation Resources (folder 2 of 2))
    - Recreation Division: Kerr Lake (folder 1 of 2), 1971-1973; 3837; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recreation Division: Kerr Lake (folder 1 of 2))
    - Recreation Division: Kerr Lake (folder 2 of 2), 1969-1973; 3838; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recreation Division: Kerr Lake (folder 2 of 2))
    - Science and Technology, 1967-1976; 3839; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Science and Technology)
    - Travel and Promotion, 1972-1973; 3840; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Travel and Promotion)
    - Water and Air Resources: Administrative Services, 1972-1973; 3841; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Water and Air Resources: Administrative Services)
    - Water and Air Resources: Air Quality Division, 1973; 3842; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Water and Air Resources: Air Quality Division)
    - Water and Air Resources: Planning Division, 1972-1974; 3843; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Water and Air Resources: Planning Division)
    - Water and Air Resources: State Grants Program, 1971; 3844; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Water and Air Resources: State Grants Program)
    - Water and Air Resources: Water Management Division, 1970-1973; 3845; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Water and Air Resources: Water Management Division)
    - Water and Air Resources: Waterways and Seashore Division, 1973; 3846; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Water and Air Resources: Waterways and Seashore Division)
    - Wildlife Resources Commission: Administration Services (folder 1 of 2), 1966-1973; 3847; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Wildlife Resources Commission: Administration Services (folder 1 of 2))
    - Wildlife Resources Commission: Administration Services (folder 2 of 2), 1966-1973; 3848; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Wildlife Resources Commission: Administration Services (folder 2 of 2))
    - Wildlife Resources Commission: Education, 1970-1973; 3849; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Wildlife Resources Commission: Education)
    - Wildlife Resources Commission: Division of Game, 1970-1973; 3850; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Wildlife Resources Commission: Division of Game)
    - Wildlife Resources Commission: Inland Fisheries, 1972-1973; 3851; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Wildlife Resources Commission: Inland Fisheries)
    - Wildlife Resources Commission: Motorboats and Water Safety, 1967-1973; 3852; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Wildlife Resources Commission: Motorboats and Water Safety)
    - Wildlife Resources Commission: Protection Division, 1972-1973; 3853; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Wildlife Resources Commission: Protection Division)
  - Public Instruction, Department of, 13; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Accounting Division, 1972-1973; 3854; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Accounting Division)
    - Agency Services, 1970-1974; 3855; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Agency Services)
    - Business Affairs, undated; 3856; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Business Affairs)
    - Consolidation of School Districts, 1972-1973; 3857; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Consolidation of School Districts)
    - Controller's Office, 1972-1975; 3858; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Controller's Office)
    - Controller's Office: Auditing and Accounting, 1973; 3859; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Controller's Office: Auditing and Accounting)
    - Controller's Office: Data Processing, 1970-1973; 3860; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Controller's Office: Data Processing)
    - Controller's Office: Division of Personnel, 1973; 3861; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Controller's Office: Division of Personnel)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974; 3862; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Correspondence)
    - Equipment Section (folder 1 of 2), 1969-1973; 3863; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Equipment Section (folder 1 of 2))
    - Equipment Section (folder 2 of 2), 1968-1973; 3864; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Equipment Section (folder 2 of 2))
    - Executive Committee, 1973; 3865; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Executive Committee)
    - Implementation Progress Report, 1974-1975; 3866; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Implementation Progress Report)
    - Insurance Division, 1972-1973; 3867; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Insurance Division)
    - Introduction, 1973; 3868; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Introduction)
    - Management Information, 1970-1973; 3869; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Management Information)
    - Plant Operation, 1973; 3870; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Plant Operation)
    - Program Services, 1973; 3871; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Program Services)
    - Recommendations: Implemented, 1974; 3872; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Implemented)
    - Recommendations: In Process, 1973-1975; 3873; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: In Process)
    - Recommendations: More Study, 1973; 3874; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: More Study)
    - Recommendations: Unacceptable, 1973-1974; 3875; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Unacceptable)
    - Research and Development, 1973; 3876; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Research and Development)
    - Reorganization, 1970-1972; 3877; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Reorganization)
    - Team 6 Reports (folder 1 of 3), 1973; 3878; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Team 6 Reports (folder 1 of 3))
    - Team 6 Reports (folder 2 of 3), 1973; 3879; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Team 6 Reports (folder 2 of 3))
    - Team 6 Reports (folder 3 of 3), 1973; 3880; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Team 6 Reports (folder 3 of 3))
    - Team 6 Roster and Member Information, 1973; 3881; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Team 6 Roster and Member Information)
    - Special Services, 1973; 3882; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Special Services)
    - State Board of Education, 1972-1973; 3883; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Board of Education)
    - Teacher Allotment and General Control, 1971-1973; 3884; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Teacher Allotment and General Control)
    - Team Meetings, 1973; 3885; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Team Meetings)
    - Textbook Division, 1969-1973; 3886; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Textbook Division)
    - Transportation Division: School Buses (folder 1 of 2), 1966-1972; 3887; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Transportation Division: School Buses (folder 1 of 2))
    - Transportation Division: School Buses (folder 2 of 2), 1971-1973; 3888; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Transportation Division: School Buses (folder 2 of 2))
  - Revenue, Department of, 14; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Revenue (folder 1 of 2), 1972-1973; 3889; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Revenue (folder 1 of 2))
    - Revenue (folder 2 of 2), 1973-1975; 3890; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Revenue (folder 2 of 2))
    - Accounting Division, 1971-1973; 3891; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Accounting Division)
    - Ad Valorem Tax Division (folder 1 of 2), 1969-1973; 3892; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Ad Valorem Tax Division (folder 1 of 2))
    - Ad Valorem Tax Division (folder 2 of 2), 1973; 3893; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Ad Valorem Tax Division (folder 2 of 2))
    - Corporate Income and Franchise Tax, 1962-1973; 3894; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Corporate Income and Franchise Tax)
    - Data Processing Subcommittee, 1972-1973; 3895; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Data Processing Subcommittee)
    - Field Audit and Collection, 1969-1973; 3896; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Field Audit and Collection)
    - Gasoline Tax, 1969-1973; 3897; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Gasoline Tax)
    - Implementation Progress, 1973-1975; 3898; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Implementation Progress)
    - Individual Income Tax Division, 1971-1973; 3899; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Individual Income Tax Division)
    - Inheritance and Gift Tax Division, 1963-1972; 3900; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Inheritance and Gift Tax Division)
    - Intangibles Tax Division, 1963-1973; 3901; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Intangibles Tax Division)
    - Introduction, 1973; 3902; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Introduction)
    - Privilege License, Beverage and Cigarette Tax Division (folder 1 of 2), 1969-1976; 3903; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Privilege License, Beverage and Cigarette Tax Division (folder 1 of 2))
    - Privilege License, Beverage and Cigarette Tax Division (folder 2 of 2), 1970-1973; 3904; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Privilege License, Beverage and Cigarette Tax Division (folder 2 of 2))
    - Recommendations: Implemented, 1973-1974; 3905; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Implemented)
    - Recommendations: In Process, 1974-1975; 3906; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: In Process)
    - Recommendations: More Study, 1973-1975; 3907; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: More Study)
    - Recommendations: Unacceptable, 1972-1974; 3908; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Unacceptable)
    - Sale and Use Tax Division, 1965-1973; 3909; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Sale and Use Tax Division)
    - Tax Research, 1973; 3910; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Tax Research)
  - Secretary of State, Department of, 15; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Secretary of State, 1972-1973; 3911; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Secretary of State)
    - Implementation Progress Report, 1974; 3912; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Implementation Progress Report)
  - Social Rehabilitation and Control, Department of, 16; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Administrative Files (folder 1 of 2), 1972-1973; 3913; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Files (folder 1 of 2))
    - Administrative Files (folder 2 of 2), 1972-1973; 3914; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Files (folder 2 of 2))
    - Audit Report, 1970-1971; 3915; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Audit Report)
    - Health Services Operation, 1972; 3916; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services Operation)
    - Implementation Progress Report, 1973-1974; 3917; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Implementation Progress Report)
    - Individual Recommendation Reports, 1973; 3918; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Individual Recommendation Reports)
    - Information, undated; 3919; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Information)
    - Introduction, 1973; 3920; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Introduction)
    - Memorandums, 1974; 3921; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Memorandums)
    - Paroles and Probation: Research Files, 1967-1973; 3922; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Paroles and Probation: Research Files)
    - Paroles and Probation: Supervision, 1970-1973; 3923; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Paroles and Probation: Supervision)
    - Prison Enterprises, 1973; 3924; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Prison Enterprises)
    - Recommendations: Implemented, 1973-1974; 3925; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Implemented)
    - Recommendations: In Process, 1973-1976; 3926; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: In Process)
    - Research Files (folder 1 of 2), 1971-1973; 3927; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Research Files (folder 1 of 2))
    - Research Files (folder 2 of 2), 1972-1973; 3928; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Research Files (folder 2 of 2))
    - Research and Planning Division, 3929; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Research and Planning Division)
    - Secretary's Office, 1972-1973; 3930; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Secretary's Office)
    - Youth Development, 1968-1973; 3931; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Youth Development)
    - Youth Development: Biennial Report, 1970-1972; 3932; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Youth Development: Biennial Report)
    - Youth Development: Miscellaneous (folder 1 of 3), 1971-1975; 3933; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Youth Development: Miscellaneous (folder 1 of 3))
    - Youth Development: Miscellaneous (folder 2 of 3), 1966-1973; 3934; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Youth Development: Miscellaneous (folder 2 of 3))
    - Youth Development: Miscellaneous (folder 3 of 3), 1971-1973; 3935; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Youth Development: Miscellaneous (folder 3 of 3))
  - Transportation, Department of, 17; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Administrative Materials (folder 1 of 2), 1973; 3936; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Materials (folder 1 of 2))
    - Administrative Materials (folder 2 of 2), 1973; 3937; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Materials (folder 2 of 2))
    - Administrative Materials, Introduction, 1973; 3938; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Materials, Introduction)
    - Assistant Chief Engineer, Construction and Maintenance, 1973; 3939; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Assistant Chief Engineer, Construction and Maintenance)
    - Branch Auditing, 1973-1974; 3940; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Branch Auditing)
    - Branch Inspection, undated; 3941; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Branch Inspection)
    - Bridge Construction, 1973; 3942; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Bridge Construction)
    - Bridge Design, 1973; 3943; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Bridge Design)
    - Bridge Location and Hydraphic Department, 1973; 3944; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Bridge Location and Hydraphic Department)
    - Bridge Maintenance, 1973; 3945; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Bridge Maintenance)
    - Central Maintenance Department, 1973; 3946; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Central Maintenance Department)
    - Construction Department, undated; 3947; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Construction Department)
    - Engineer Division, 1973; 3948; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division)
    - Engineer Division 1, 1971-1973; 3949; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division 1)
    - Engineer Division 2, 1973; 3950; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division 2)
    - Engineer Division 3, 1973; 3951; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division 3)
    - Engineer Division 4, 1973; 3952; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division 4)
    - Engineer Division 5, 1973; 3953; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division 5)
    - Engineer Division 6, 1973; 3954; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division 6)
    - Engineer Division 7, 1973; 3955; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division 7)
    - Engineer Division 8, 1973; 3956; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division 8)
    - Engineer Division 9, 1973; 3957; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division 9)
    - Engineer Division 10, 1972-1973; 3958; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division 10)
    - Engineer Division 11, 1973; 3959; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division 11)
    - Engineer Division 12, 1970-1973; 3960; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division 12)
    - Engineer Division 13, 1970-1973; 3961; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division 13)
    - Engineer Division 14, 1973; 3962; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division 14)
    - Engineer Division, General, 1972; 3963; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Engineer Division, General)
    - Equipment Department, 1972-1973; 3964; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Equipment Department)
    - Equipment Department: Allocation of Funds, 1971-1973; 3965; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Equipment Department: Allocation of Funds)
    - Equipment Department: Data, 1972-1973; 3966; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Equipment Department: Data)
    - Equipment Department: Manpower Listings, 1972-1973; 3967; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Equipment Department: Manpower Listings)
    - Equipment Department: Rental Policy Manual, 1972; 3968; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Equipment Department: Rental Policy Manual)
    - Ferry Operations, 1970; 3969; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Ferry Operations)
    - Financial Security, 1972-1973; 3970; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Financial Security)
    - Fiscal Department (folder 1 of 3), 1968-1973; 3971; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Fiscal Department (folder 1 of 3))
    - Fiscal Department (folder 2 of 3), 1968-1973; 3972; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Fiscal Department (folder 2 of 3))
    - Fiscal Department (folder 3 of 3), 1968-1973; 3973; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Fiscal Department (folder 3 of 3))
    - Functions and Manning Charts, undated; 3974; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Functions and Manning Charts)
    - General Information, 1972; 3975; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder General Information)
    - Governor's Aviation Commission, 1973; 3976; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Governor's Aviation Commission)